mymediads.com 2019-10-06

# Privacy Policy | MyMediAds

This Policy explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by the operators of MyMediAds (the “Site”). By visiting the Site and providing any information, you consent to this Policy, as may be modified by us from time to time.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site, either voluntarily or as connected to your use of the Site. For example, we may collect information, such as your name, e-mail address, title and others. When you visit the Site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your IP address, your computer’s operating system, the browser type and the address of a referring website. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above.

COOKIES

Cookies may be used by our Site. These are small data files that are stored on a user’s computer and enable the site to recognize users who have previously visited them and retain certain information such as customer preferences, emails and history.

You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of the Site will be limited.

We may collect web log data (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, such as non-human readable form email address.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS

We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Site or operate certain Site pages and features. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other Web sites, your IP address, your ISP and the browser you use to visit our Site. They do this using cookies, clear gifs or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. Publishing an ad on the website means that you have read the terms and conditions and you’re fully aware of the fact that MyMediAds may use the personal information for newsletters and third parties/ advertisers, and the user shall not have any claims against MyMediAds.

HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

In general, we use personal information we collect to process your requests or transactions, to provide you with information or services you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site and the services. For example, we may use the information we collect:

  * to provide you with all of the services, features, and functionality included within the services, to provide other services or information you request and to complete any transactions in connection therewith;
  * to respond to your e-mails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;
  * to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications, products and services;
  * to personalize and improve Site content and features and your experience on the Site, such as providing ads, content or features to match your profile and interests;
  * to contact you about our or a third party’s services, products, activities, special events or offers and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes.

Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our partners.  If you wish to request that we no longer use your information, contact us via the “contact” form on the site. Following such request, the use of your information shall be as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

SHARING INFORMATION

You understand that when you use the services, certain information you post on publicly available portions of the Site may be shared with other users and posted on other portions of the Site, including without limitation your comments to articles, name, profile details, images, and messages to other users on the Site. Your use of the services constitutes your consent to share this information in such manner and all such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information when posting comments or other information or content to the Site or through the service, this information may become publicly available and may be collected and used by others. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information.   We may share information with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Site and the services.

We may disclose information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process or authorities, respond to lawful requests, any claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of, our users, our employees or the public. Information may also be disclosed during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership.
